Isabelle Hallin Papers MS219
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Isabelle Hallin papers, 1912 -- 2013; MS219.001; 2.9 Linear Feet; 5 Digital Object(s)
  - Isabelle Hallin in fur coat and headshots, 1935 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 4 of 49)
    - Isabelle Hallin in fur coat, 1935 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00004.00001 (Box 2)
      photographic prints
  - Isabelle Hallin 8th grade class group photograph, 1925; MS219.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 5 of 49)
  - Unidentified group photograph, 1933 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 6 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin styling another woman's hair, 1929 -- 1935; MS219.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 7 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin Jackson College freshman photograph and theater group photo, 1930; MS219.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 8 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin headshot, 1930 -- 1935; MS219.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 9 of 49)
  - Jackson College group photograph, 1930 -- 1933; MS219.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 10 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin headshot and unidentified group photo, 1930 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 11 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin photograph, 1933 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 12 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin photograph, 1933 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 13 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin photograph, 1933 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 14 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin high school photograph, 1929; MS219.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 15 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin and miscellaneous photographs, 1930 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 16 of 49)
  - Photos from unidentified theater production, 1925 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 17 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin as lead acress in "the Wran", 1935; MS219.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 18 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin in white dress with glasses, 1925 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 19 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin wearing top hat and gloves, 1925 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 20 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin with ruler and book, 1925 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 21 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin and her father C. Fred Hallin looking over petitions, 1937; MS219.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 22 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin drinking milk, 1930 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 23 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin looking at petitions, 1937; MS219.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 24 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin with Neck Kerchief, 1930 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 25 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin with glasses, laughing, 1925 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 26 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin age 26, 1938 -- 1939; MS219.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 27 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin press photo with unidentified men, 1937; MS219.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 28 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin, C. Fred Hallin, and unidentified man, 1937; MS219.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 29 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin and supporters outside Saugus Town Hall, 1937; MS219.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 30 of 49). Caption on back of photograph reads: "A personal triumph was scored by Isabelle Hallin, Saugus high school teacher, as she presented her side of school committee ousting to a crowd of 1200 in Saugus town hall last night. She is seen being cheered by youthful supporters as she left the demonstration."
  - Isabelle Hallin in car, 1937; MS219.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 31 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin using sewing machine, 1935 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 32 of 49)
  - Pro-Isabelle Hallin student demonstration, 1937-07-08; MS219.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 33 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin smiling in car, 1937; MS219.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 34 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin assisted from home by father C. Fred Hallin, 1937; MS219.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 35 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin and C. Fred Hallin, 1937; MS219.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 36 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin with two unidentified men, 1937; MS219.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 37 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin standing near painting, 1937 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 38 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin holding books, 1933 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 39 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin photo, 1933 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 40 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin photo, 1933 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 41 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin walking with C. Fred Hallin, 1937 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 42 of 49)
  - Miss Isabelle Hallin, ousted school teacher, 1937 -- 1938; MS219.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 43 of 49)
  - Stella M. Crater and Isabelle Halline at NBC audition, 1937-08-07; MS219.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 44 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin on telephone, 1937; MS219.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 45 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin with books, 1937; MS219.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 46 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin sitting in white dress, 1938; MS219.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 47 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin Saugus school teacher, 1937; MS219.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 48 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin sitting in white dress, 1938; MS219.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
    (Pictures binder 49 of 49)
  - Isabelle Hallin childhood framed photograph, 1917 -- 1927; MS219.001.002.00050 (Box 2)
  - Hallin, Isabelle L. J1933 photographs, 1933 -- 1941; MS219.001.002.00051 (Box 2)
  - Isabelle Hallin college scrapbook, 1929 -- 1935; MS219.001.003.00001 (Box Shared 135)
    This scrapbook was compiled by Isabelle Hallin and primarily contains items from her time as a student at Jackson College (1930-33). The book contains photographs of Hallin, news clippings about classmates, a variety of fraternity booklets, and theater programs from Pen Paint and Pretzels.
  - Isabelle Hallin high school diploma from Saugus High School, 1929; MS219.001.003.00002 (Box Large Map Case 3 Drawer 1)
  - Tufts and Jackson Class of 1933 graduation photograph, MS219.001.003.00003 (Box Large Map Case 3 Drawer 1)
    This is a panorama photograph of the Tufts College and Jackson College graduating classes of 1933. Isabelle Hallin is identified in the photograph.